<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Miscellaneous on Fsu0413&#39;s Original Qt builds</title>
    <link>/miscellaneous/index.html</link>
    <description>Recent content in Miscellaneous on Fsu0413&#39;s Original Qt builds</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><atom:link href="/miscellaneous/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Notes for this repo</title>
      <link>/miscellaneous/notes-for-this-repo/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/miscellaneous/notes-for-this-repo/index.html</guid>
      <description>Chinese / Multilingual Support This website was English only since when it was initially built, although the maintainer of this website (me, Fsu0413) is a Chinese native speaker from the PRC.
Currently I am gradually adding Simplified Chinese support on this website.
Recently this website has gained multilingual support thanks to the built-in multilingual support of Hugo and the recently switched Relearn theme.
Current Chinese support is in the stage of writing texts.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Current build status</title>
      <link>/miscellaneous/current-build-status/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/miscellaneous/current-build-status/index.html</guid>
      <description>QQtPatcher Support Status This is a list where QQtPatcher is supported and tested on.
Other version may work, but also may silently fail.
A valid qbp.json is needed for patching Qt 4 Series since qmake -query don&amp;rsquo;t output the makespec.
Qt 5.14 is relocatable as announced in New Features in Qt 5.14, so Qt after 5.14 won&amp;rsquo;t need QQtPatcher anymore.
I delivered QQtPatcher for earlier version of 5.14 (because of the fact that I forgot to modify QQtPatcher related code in build scripts).</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Current failures</title>
      <link>/miscellaneous/current-failures/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/miscellaneous/current-failures/index.html</guid>
      <description>QDoc after Qt 5.12 cannot use static linked clang when using MSVC It uses libclang_static.lib but clang don&amp;rsquo;t provide this one.
I have decided not provide LLVM-based QDoc until I find a way to static link it.
Update 2020.11.3:
libclang_static.lib is packed seprately using script by Qt guys.
Thanks &amp;ldquo;lixinwei&amp;rdquo; on QTCN.org for telling me related info. Original post (Sorry, it&amp;rsquo;s in Chinese)
Command line too long when building Qt 6.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Previous Histories</title>
      <link>/miscellaneous/histories/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/miscellaneous/histories/index.html</guid>
      <description>2022.10.4 Update Qt 6.4.0.
Update Qt 6.2.4 static builds with static runtime. Previous versions are without it.
Update Qt 6.2.4 LLVM-MinGW builds built with llvm 15.
Qt 6.3 builds are removed.
2022.9.16 Update Qt 6.2.4 / 5.15.6 with updated patch of CVE-2022-37434. Qt 6.2 are rebuilt with QtWebEngine 6.3.2.
Update to Xcode 14 and rebuild all of macOS hosted Qt 6.2 onwards.
2022.9.12 Update Qt 6.2.4 / 6.3.2 WebAssembly packages. They are currently built using PCH.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>