<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Miscellaneous on Fsu0413&#39;s Original Qt builds</title>
    <link>/miscellaneous/index.html</link>
    <description>Recent content in Miscellaneous on Fsu0413&#39;s Original Qt builds</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><atom:link href="/miscellaneous/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Notes for this repo</title>
      <link>/miscellaneous/notes-for-this-repo/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/miscellaneous/notes-for-this-repo/index.html</guid>
      <description>Reproduciable building I use a set of scripts to do the build and packaging for reproducible building Qt.
If you are interested in build method, please check the following GitHub repo.
GitHub
However unfortunely, this website is manually edited.
Source of this site is:
GitHub
Notes on static builds I don&amp;rsquo;t use static builds in huge projects. I don&amp;rsquo;t think it is wise to use a static build there.
Maybe you just want to distribute a single portable executable binary file, but there is limitations:</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Current build status</title>
      <link>/miscellaneous/current-build-status/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/miscellaneous/current-build-status/index.html</guid>
      <description>QQtPatcher Support Status This is a list where QQtPatcher is supported and tested on.
Other version may work, but also may silently fail.
A valid qbp.json is needed for patching Qt 4 Series since qmake -query don&amp;rsquo;t output the makespec.
Qt 5.14 is relocatable as announced in New Features in Qt 5.14, so Qt after 5.14 won&amp;rsquo;t need QQtPatcher anymore.
I delivered QQtPatcher for earlier version of 5.14 (because of the fact that I forgot to modify QQtPatcher related code in build scripts).</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Current failures</title>
      <link>/miscellaneous/current-failures/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/miscellaneous/current-failures/index.html</guid>
      <description>Qt 5.12 WebAssembly builds can&amp;rsquo;t built with OpenSSL Both qsslsocket_opensslpre11.cpp and qsslsocket_openssl11.cpp includes qlibrary.h which is not usable in WebAssembly platform.
Since -openssl and -openssl-linked both use this file, so we can only use -no-ssl&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;.
I didn&amp;rsquo;t try with Qt 5.15 series, but qsslsocket_openssl.cpp in Qt 5.15 includes qlibrary.h as well&amp;hellip;
I didn&amp;rsquo;t try with Qt 6.2 onwards.
Update 2022.11.6:
I gave up supporting SSL on WebAssembly and will remove this item later.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Previous Histories</title>
      <link>/miscellaneous/histories/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/miscellaneous/histories/index.html</guid>
      <description>2022.10.4 Update Qt 6.4.0.
Update Qt 6.2.4 static builds with static runtime. Previous versions are without it.
Update Qt 6.2.4 llvm-mingw builds built with llvm 15.
Qt 6.3 builds are removed.
2022.9.16 Update Qt 6.2.4 / 5.15.6 with updated patch of CVE-2022-37434. Qt 6.2 are rebuilt with QtWebEngine 6.3.2.
Update to Xcode 14 and rebuild all of macOS hosted Qt 6.2 onwards.
2022.9.12 Update Qt 6.2.4 / 6.3.2 WebAssembly packages. They are currently built using PCH.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>